Erick Emanuel Vicentin

Contact

Birthday: 01/12/1996

Email: <u>erickvicentin14@hotmail.com</u> Telephone: +54 (362) 5227229

Career Summary

Erick has been working as a Test Automation Engineer since July 2020 working with technologies like Java & JUnit, Gradle, Spring, Javascript, WebDriverIO, Cucumber and Selenium, specifically automating API and E2E test cases. Currently, he is focused on creating and running automated front-end / web-ui tests. It is also responsible for the daily monitoring of the results of the automated test suite, the reporting of errors found to the development team, and the help in detecting their origin and their resolution. Previously, he was dedicated to developing in React.js, working on an internal Globant project, the StarMeUp component suite. He already has experience in some Front Tech (ReactJS, React-Native, based on javascript) to have more than one profile. He has solid knowledge in the use of the Git versioning system, and has worked as a team with agile methodologies.

Summary of Qualifications

Skills:

- HTML
- JavaScript (ES6+)
- CSS
- React.js
- React-Native
- MySQL
- Java
- Selenium
- Git GitHub
- Bitbucket
- OOP
- NodeJS
- NPM
- MongoDB
- WebdriverIO
- Cucumber
- Postman
- GCP

Languages

- Spanish (Native)
- English (Intermediate)

Career History

Globant, Resistencia, Argentina

Test Automation Engineer Semi Senior (LATAM Airlines)

My tasks include:

- Everything previously mentioned.
- Monitor bug resolution efforts and track successes.
- Work with project teams to identify, triage and isolate defects and issues in all environments and retesting.
- Propose improvements to the automated framework used and, if approved, develop those improvements.

October 2021 – Actually

Globant, Resistencia, Argentina

February 2021 – September 2021

Test Automation Engineer Junior Advance (LATAM Airlines)

Test Automation Engineer at NDC product for travel agencies (Web UI Testing), my tasks include:

- Creates and executes test cases, including identification and tracking issues through resolution. Using WebDriverIO, Selenium, Javascript, Nodejs, Allure & Cucumber.
- Create Automated Test Cases using a team standard framework.
- Execute Automated Test cases and perform the necessary maintenance to it.
- Document software defects and report defects to software developers.
- Monitor periodically Automated execution of Test Cases identifying product defects and/or necessary maintenance
- Collaborate with software engineers and testers to refine/improve our continuous delivery systems for on-premise and cloud technologies and to influence test strategies.

Globant, Resistencia, Argentina

October 2020 - January 2021

Test Automation Engineer Junior

- API Testing for NDC Product (LATAM Airlines).
- Create Automated Test Cases using a team standard framework and technologies like Java, Spring, JUnit and Gradle.
- Execute Automated Test cases and perform the necessary maintenance to it.

Globant, Resistencia, Argentina

March 2020 - September 2020

Test Automation Engineer Trainee

• Creating test cases in Java using Selenium WebDriver in TAE Academy.

Globant, Resistencia, Argentina

April 2020 – July 2020

ReactJS Developer (StarMeUp - Globant Project)

- StarMeUp OS empowers employees to become the best versions of themselves, and become even more significant contributors for the organization, by helping them overcome natural human limitations through technology and AI.
- Currently working as front-end developer, for a cross platform for the main product that Globant is developing. The product is developed using React, Redux and Redux-Sagas as main technologies.

Our approach is to work creating cross react components, so all project applications can use them.

Apex America, Resistencia, Argentina

December 2017 – February 2020

Customer Services Representative.

- Attention to Cablevision-Fibertel customers.
- Sale of products and services.
- Administrative tasks of invoicing, registration of claims, attention in general.
- First line technical support in tv and internet service.

•

Multicontrol, Gral. San Martin - CHACO, Argentina

January 2015 – March 2017

Administration manager.

- Billing of works-products-services.
- Elaboration of personalized budgets.
- Control of attendance of the personnel and liquidation of salaries.
- Load of technical orders for factory guarantees.
- Direct contact with suppliers and factories that the company represents.
- Elaboration of forms and operation manuals regarding guarantees attended.

Education

UTN F.R.Re, Resistencia, Argentina

Degree title: Information Systems Engineering. Intermediate title: Universitary Systems Analyst.

E.E.S. N° 71, Gral. san Martin - CHACO, Argentina

March 2009 - December 2014

March 2015 – Present

Polymodal Bachelor with orientation in Naturals and Exact Science.

• Best average in Mathematics.

Courses

- The complete Node.js developer course (3rd Edition) (Udemy June 2020)
- The complete Javascript course 2020: build real projects! (Udemy June 2020)
- React-Redux (Acamica April 2020).
- Introduction to TestNG (Test Automation University March 2020).
- Mobile Testing (Acamica March 2020).
- Selenium WebDriver with Java (Test Automation University March 2020).
- Git and Git-Hub Professional Course (Platzi February 2020).
- Object Oriented Java SE Course (Platzi February 2020).
- React JS Course (Platzi February 2020).
- Web Element Locator Strategies Course (Test Automation University February 2020).
- Java Programming Course (Test Automation University October 2019).